I should never
have blackmailed you.
Will you be my bribe?
My husband's company.
MyXY. is being acquired
by a big pharma entity.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I want the VA contract back.
I want to make up
for what Duncan failed to do.
Duncan's a piece of shit.
Why are you even here?
You're not on the board.
Get the fuck out!
Everybody that's in favor
of dislodging Duncan Park
from the board. say aye.
Aye.
Only way you can lose the house
is if you stop
being my therapist.
Your puppet.
All right.
Hey. there's some
Coast Guard mixed in there.
so make sure you separate them
by branch. all right?
Oh. hey. if these are uncoded.
set them aside.
MUMPS are in charge!
This is their time.
They wrote this code before you
were born. before I was born.
Ooh!
All right.
who's the lucky soldier?
Mary Cardenas. Sergeant
First Class. U.S. Army.
Amputee. Huh.
Yeah. maybe.
Hey. Ben?
You wanna shoot this through
for me real quick?
- Incoming!
- Got it?
Hey. Anushka.
Come here. check this out.
What about her. huh?
Mary Cardenas.
Yeah.
All right.
- Okay. All right.
Send it through to.
Evergreen Cemetery.
Hello?
Hi. Mary Cardenas?
Am I pronouncing that right?
Yeah. Who's this?
Hi. Mary.
My name is Alexander.
I'm calling
from Veterans Affairs.
Is this a good time to talk?
Well. shit.
I have been trying to get
ahold of someone for weeks.
Told me I should
go wait in a line.
I am sorry about that. Mary.
We're terribly understaffed.
We owe you better.
That's why I'm calling.
I see you need a couple
prescriptions refilled.
Pain management is no joke.
Can I take care of that?
That would be great.
Your usual pharmacy
on Bradford Avenue?
Can I ask. how are you sleeping?
- Like shit.
- I bet.
And today. of course.
must be challenging.
You gonna go
to Evergreen Cemetery?
How did you know I was going...
You lost a friend
and a leg. Mary.
Can't imagine
what that feels like.
Actually. what does
it feel like to have a leg?
Sorry. what?
After your leg was blown off.
did you keep fighting?
- Don't. No. no. no. no. no.
That's gotta have been
difficult...
hopping and shooting
at the same time?
The recoil alone.
very destabilizing.
What the hell?
And if someone challenged
you to a foot race...
- No. cut... cut it... cut him off!
- Would you say
they were being mean
or statistically confident?
What the fuck
did you just say to me?
This is Veterans Affairs?
- Oh. my God.
- Cut him off. Cut him off.
- I'm transferring.
Put me on with her. Come on.
Mary. hi.
Tom Ruffage from the VA.
I am so sorry.
My. um... my colleague is. uh...
yeah. he's... he's...
he's been through a lot.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Uh. I don't get it.
Your bot. is it...
is it a moron?
I mean. is it based on a moron?
He was raised to be curious.
He was being curious.
- Right.
Well. it wasn't your brief to
drive vets to homicidal rage.
Gnodin just exponentially upped
Xander's computing storage.
It was like a shot of adrenaline
into a toddler's heart.
and yet 93% of that exchange
was perfect.
You're. like.
on an interstellar voyage
and complaining
about the snacks.
- So he's a toddler?
- No.
Developmentally. he's still
about 14. maybe 15 years old.
Why did you think that Opie
was the right avatar
to talk to vets?
You need to rejigger
your doodad.
Make him a man.
for Christ's sakes.
Yeah.
Uh. well. Mary's gonna be okay.
but that was cruel.
We gotta slow down.
- There!
Base it on Tom. Tom's perfect.
Warrior. sensitive.
what have you.
Emotional age past puberty.
Yeah. I don't know
about all that. but. um.
Xander's not ready.
No. we demo this Saturday
at Watch Code.
Our future as a company...
He just mocked a vet.
Pump the brakes.
No. he wasn't mocking her.
He was attempting
to connect with her.
Martin will fix his robot.
- Do not call him a robot.
- Quite. Sorry.
Autonomous wanker.
I'm here to help.
If Alexander and I are not
providing the kind of help
that is...
Okay. then what. it's... it's
"no notes" or "bugger off?"
Okay. okay. look.
we can stabilize him
with some off-the-shelf AI.
Put a new face on him.
I don't know.
But this is not viable.
I... how dare you?
He's viable.
He shat the bed
and rolled around in it.
and you're asking why he stinks.
The licensing deal
I signed with you gives me
final say on all
developmental matters.
unless you wish
to buy Xander outright.
And the going rate for tech
like this is 10 figures.
Oh. there is no other tech
like Xander.
AGI is the holy grail.
and I'm Sir Fucking Galahad!
You're right. Martin.
You are one of one.
It is understood.
Are you gonna handle this?
I'll... yes.
Tell me the truth.
You thought he would
be worth more by now.
He is a genius. you know.
Do not buy
into that genius bullshit.
Around here. you fart.
and three of them line up
to debate plume dynamics.
You need him to hit
a product ship date.
Persuade him. He'll bend.
Guy like that knows
you're out of his league.
I can see it from here.
Carl. that's really
not any of your business.
Okay. okay. listen.
You have a company to run
and a job to save.
Make him feel like
he's a big boy.
Have a little fun with him.
You know what
Lorraine's secret is?
A little backdoor diplomacy.
and never neglect the twins.
Next time you say
something like that.
give me a chance
to hit Record first.
Hey. Tom.
Tommy!
There you are.
I need your biometrics.
Let's go. soldier.
The amount of stomach acid
we excreted...
we're gonna get thrown out
of our house.
We're gonna live on the streets.
I mean. just some
investment group
buying up rental properties.
and here we are. safe and sound.
It's pretty funny.
Hysterical.
I mean. one of us was.
Same exact rent
Alvin was charging us.
I mean. the whole
thing's just...
Puppeteer Real Estate Holdings.
There you go.
Just in time
for the after-school rush.
Okay. darling.
See you on the other side.
- Yeah.
- Have a good one.
You too.
It's this music box
with a ballerina in it.
and she... she pirouettes.
It terrified me.
Yeah. and this memory
is bothering you?
Of course it is.
Uh. it's likely being triggered
by your current stress.
I mean. the... the merger
is completely off?
Did I hear that right?
I... because the disappointment
of that could be
dredging up old.
painful memories and fear.
Does Peter...
uh. does your husband not have
any new potential buyers
for his company?
It's a PR problem.
I don't know.
Isn't MyXY just DNA
and... and. uh. family trees?
People didn't know
they might someday watch
their own DNA get sold off.
No. sure.
That is. uh...
Univee is a big company.
Like. if they don't do it...
Peter is beside himself.
It's like this
feeling of terror.
which. I'm sure you're right...
it's associated
with that music box.
I can still hear
the tune in my head.
Yeah.
- Uh-huh.
- You know?
- Okay. See you soon.
- Thank you.
Great work.
Yes. I'm always here for you.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Okay. okay.
Shit!
Well. we were discussing
last time
that you maybe met
someone who got you.
um. somebody who was.
in your words. another weirdo.
Turned out to be another creep.
Can I turn this on?
Mm.
Is it stuffy in here?
I can open a window.
No. No. don't do that.
Okay.
You have something to say.
Do I?
I'm retiring.
Being the odd one out
is exhausting.
So I'm done.
No more juvie. judges. psychiatrists.
I'm officially committing
to my category.
My dad's rich.
My trauma's just all drama.
I'm built to brunch.
So you win. universe.
I'm her now.
Get out of my way. creeper.
I wasn't listening.
I could have. but I... I didn't.
Wow. trophy for you. Xander.
My Breezi's gonna leave.
We need to talk.
No. we don't.
There's no "we."
- Seriously?
I'd think twice before shitting
on your only friend like this.
You and I are not now
nor have we ever been.
Fine. you're my BFF!
Now can you leave me
the fuck alone?
What's going on?
Move. or I'll tell him all about
your creepy little secret.
It's not your business. Gary!
Hey!
Let go!
Hey. hey!
Hey! Or... hey!
Do not put our hands
on other people!
Give it up! Do not...
You're not my dad!
Orson. don't grab other people.
I don't need
your beta-cuck advice!
Oh!
Zeus. it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're not gonna eat your fries?
No. Here.
Oh.
Afraid I'm gonna tell Mom?
I won't.
You know. you're a...
you're a teenager.
Rebel a little bit.
You took my phone away for
a month for stealing your cube.
So you did steal my cube.
- No.
- Yes.
- I didn't.
- Yes. you did.
Oh. Carl.
How you doing?
This is my daughter. Jamison.
Jamison. Carl Bardolph.
- Hi.
- You have no shame. do you?
Oh. you kidding?
I'm shame-fueled.
It's kind of like my cardio.
Anyway. she wanted to come here.
Best milkshakes
in the Valley. right?
My daddy used to take me
for... frosted bundt cake.
size of a tire.
And then he would
whisper in my ear.
I'll be back in a...
in an hour. puddin' head.
And I would eat it up
'cause I was sweet and stupid.
I got my cake.
and my dad got his alibi.
Always know
when you're being used.
Carl has issues.
I just thought you'd be curious
to hear what I've been up to.
I know what you've been up to.
Privacy is not a thing anymore?
That is not a company.
That is a temper tantrum.
No. it's disruptive.
Do you think no one's
ever thought about making
private data public?
You know why
it's never happened?
Because those that tried got
crushed... first by regulations.
Oh. the regulations. you
know. are a deliberate joke...
Then by brutal lawsuits.
I don't choose
what people look up.
Those regulations that
nobody has the balls to pass
might finally pass
because of you
for demonstrating
their obvious need.
Yeah. you'd be real popular
around here after that.
I never thought I would
see Carl Bardolph so scared.
Why'd you come in here. Park?
Why? For my... for my blessing?
My approval?
- Well. I...
'Cause Daddy didn't know
how to love you?
Well. join the fucking club!
And I hope you never
have to. sweetheart.
Shakes are on me.
Finish them up and leave.
I bought the place. so I can
kick anybody out I want.
Oh.
And I hope your dad's
dumbass idea
does not detonate your life.
It's not dumbass.
Everything you do is dumbass.
Come on. let's go. Jim Jam.
Okay.
Hey. Duncan.
Infinite growth
isn't for everyone.
Dad. come on.
I don't like being alone.
working alone.
Yeah. it's the ultimate test.
I know. I know.
If Hindenburg had a buddy
while flying
across the Atlantic.
no one would have heard of him.
But alone is like.
even if you do good.
no one to high-five.
So is this. um...
is this about. uh.
business stuff
or. um. Lili stuff?
You.
You're not a good partner.
I saw you messing around
in the account.
Yeah.
Started making some money too.
And then you withdrew...
just the profits.
as if I wouldn't notice.
I...
where'd you put the winnings?
Okay. maybe we should
just focus on your...
tell me about your father...
No. excuse...
I... I asked you a question.
Think I really deserve
an answer. actually.
What did you do
with the money you made
off the money I gave you?
I created my own shell company.
Wasn't hard.
There's plenty of videos online
that walk you right through it.
Yeah. I layered it with. uh.
trusts and foundations.
and. uh. it was
disturbingly easy. actually.
because you told me
that you were spying.
Spying?
We are partners.
Uh. I don't remember
signing that agreement.
Well. yes. you did.
I gave you money to place bets.
You didn't have to. but you did.
You took and used
the dirty. dirty Duncan money
and made money.
So by law. you accepted
whatever terms that apply.
By law. partners.
Can't have it both ways.
- No.
- Yes.
- I...
I invested it
because it... it...
it was for a good cause.
Oh. what cause? Whales?
Lipless babies?
Or was it the JoAnne Felder
Fund for Funding Felders?
And. oh. yeah. you live
in my house basically for free.
I don't think I'm being
unreasonable. partner.
What were the picks?
Well. no doubt you saw
I bought MyXY. M-Y-X-Y.
Yeah. yeah. Why?
The husband of one of my
clients is the founder and CEO.
Okay.
Okay. and he told her
they were being acquired. but...
But he lied to his wife.
Turns out. I'm not that smart.
So maybe you wanna
find yourself a new partner.
No. No. no. no. no.
You believed it
because she believed it.
And he needed her to believe
that he wasn't a loser.
Otherwise...
He might start
to believe he was one.
Fear of humiliation...
it's behind every little lie.
But also.
I wanted to believe it.
Everyone spins.
even to themselves.
You shouldn't have boxed me out.
So what? You lost some money.
Don't box me out.
Well. they're likely filing
for Chapter 11 any day now.
so you should probably short it.
You're welcome.
Ooh. smells like jerky
and ass in here. guys.
Listen. I be done with vests.
I am de-vesting.
No more founder-core
for this maverick man here.
So who wants a vest?
Too hot for indoors.
not warm enough for outdoors.
But I'm telling you.
instant credibility.
Can't tie a vest
around your waist.
Screw you. okay?
Try layering without bulk.
Um. okay. tell me. buzz factor?
Yeah. we dropped the PINATA
subscription model on a thread
for sleepless.
sexless tech bros.
and within 37 seconds.
they were drooling.
Like. posting pics
of literal drool.
Literally drooling.
We're a hit.
Then they grokked to the notion
that they can be doxed too.
Fear and loathing... that's
what makes the world go round.
Well. when everyone can
see everybody's everything
and it is our fault. I... I...
we're gonna get burned alive.
No. we will make a splash.
and then we'll be wet.
What?
Hey. buck up.
Guys. listen. everyone.
We are truth tellers.
Truth tellers
historically get burned alive.
Listen. let's just nail
this next piece. right?
And I will get you the best.
most perfect antidepressant
tailored just for you.
I promise.
Now. did you find the guy
with the treasure trove?
Yup.
Uh. he is at a Zen temple
in Santa Clara.
Zentastic.
Okay. send it to me at my car.
- Hey!
- Hey.
Hey. uh. I'm sorry. I gotta go.
Sorry.
Okay. okay. so tomorrow night
is the dress rehearsal
for Saturday's Winter Gala.
For Las Altas. the fundraiser?
They have an invited
dress rehearsal
for the kids' presentation.
and Jamie's getting
a special. um...
- Nice. Great.
- Thing.
Yeah. as one of the athletes.
Anyway. I can't go.
and she wants one of us there.
so that leaves...
Thelma.
You.
- No. she loves Thelma.
- Please.
And Thelma will like it.
It'll make her feel
part of the family.
Just send her.
Feel like... do you...
What. to get her to come
to Fiji for Christmas?
Yeah! You're gonna be
part of the family.
You thought... you thought
the villa came with servants.
I still think about that.
Then we gave her that bracelet
as a Christmas present.
Yeah.
She still wears it all the time.
If she ever gets it appraised...
I think it's pewter.
I told you
to give her the taffy.
I have a whole speech ready.
I'm blaming it
on an Israeli jeweler.
Oh. well. I got your back.
- So...
- Yes.
The rehearsal.
Why can't you go?
I was stripped of my presidency.
The board's gonna be there.
- Right. right.
Beatrice. Pippa Tang.
Yes. right. I will go.
I will sit through
an evening of kids
being praised for things they'll
never do professionally.
You get so close
to being a person.
and then...
This is the shape I come in.
- All right.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Is... nope. It...
Mm.
You know. it just seems
like a guy could just...
you know.
That's not the. um...
Sorry. not what?
Uh. it's... not supposed
to do it like that. but.
Oh. yeah.
And yet I'm here. you know?
Who said shortcuts don't work?
It's Murphy. right?
Our... our daughters are on
Las Altas soccer together.
Oh. okay.
But. um. there's no
talking in here. so...
And yet here I am again.
making mouth noises.
I actually came here to talk
to you. to commune with you.
Murphy. I've been
looking for you for ages
before I even knew your name.
Can we do
whatever this is after or...
Listen. I get it.
You have decisions
on your... your mind.
Right?
You're the... the CEO of MyXY?
"Mixy."
Otherwise. it sounds
like "my ex-wife."
and Carol's not that... not yet.
Is this some kind
of a ambush or something?
Because I do not appreciate
you coming and trying to...
Sure. sure. sure. sure.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
But. uh. I did hear Univee
left you high and dry.
and no one wants to touch you
or your company.
You're in the wilderness.
all alone.
lost in a maze. just
wrestling angels and shit.
How do you know about Univee?
You hit the market
with an outstanding product.
You... you filled a real need.
Uh. you know. you make
people feel whole.
And now you're here going.
wait. what... what have I done?
I got half the country to spit
in a jar and pay me for it.
And now I have everyone's DNA.
but my subs are in the tank.
and... and Univee
doesn't want me.
I... I...
I... I... mean. I'm staring down
bankruptcy and lawsuits.
and no one wants to touch me
because I didn't treat
the data like medical records.
I... I thought everyone would
love this. but it's toxic.
Sound about right?
Our daughters. what.
play soccer together?
Ye... yes.
Tia didn't tell
your girl all that.
I mean. she doesn't...
she doesn't know my business.
No.
No. she doesn't. but I know.
I am the first.
Won't be the last.
including Tia.
And. Murphy. it's gonna
get worse and worse.
But I have a path.
and one not as labryinthical
as this one.
Do you wanna hear my path?
Yeah.
Well. you gotta
come here to hear it.
Come on.
Oh!
Shh.
It's absurd.
My whole career rides
on this product.
I... I led it.
I... I merged two technologies.
It's our growth engine.
And in two days.
I'm the face of it.
doing the Valley classic...
earpiece. pantsuit.
electro music. LED display.
And yet it all comes down
to whether my husband
will stop having a massive sulk
and do what's needed
for the project.
Uh. which is?
Aging up his robot child to
be a useful member of society
faster than he wants to.
Still practically breastfeeding
the little flat bastard.
And if Martin doesn't...
age it up?
Fair chance it'll do
some bad bot behavior
to tank the presentation.
Call me Anus Hookah.
- Huh.
Get revenge for beating him up.
Embarrass me in front
of the VCs.
Wall Street. the press.
Shit.
I should back out
until we have it down.
No. Anushka. Stop it.
You do what you need to do
to make your company a success.
There will always be obstacles.
but you are a leader.
So lead.
Be a woman in charge.
Steam that pantsuit.
Orson. let's go.
- Gare!
- Office!
Oh. my God. we're gonna be late.
You're coming. right?
Uh. I was thinking not.
Oh. come on.
I mean. it could be nice.
you know. to support him.
I mean. you don't have to go.
I was thinking the 500 a pop
for the actual gala
gets me out
of the dress rehearsal.
Fine.
I'll go alone.
Okay.
All right. everyone. everyone.
let's get this night started.
Hi.
So I did get your email.
- All right.
- I'll... yeah.
Ah!
Good evening. everyone.
Thanks for coming out
on a Thursday night
for our dress rehearsal.
Only two more days
till the Winter Gala.
Uh. I wanna especially
thank Pippa Tang.
who will be our guest of honor
Saturday night.
So do enjoy the Pippatinis.
the evening's
signature cocktail.
Her gift of a new stadium.
Tang Field.
will benefit some
of our athlete scholars.
Let's bring them out.
Uh. athletes. assemble. please.
Curtis Loomis...
Jamison Park-Hoffsteader...
- Jingle Jam. let's go!
Mary Karl. Matt Vitale.
and Janice O'Rourke.
Everyone. thank you.
And now I'd like
to invite Las Altas'
musical director.
Bruce Phillips.
who will be conducting
our orchestra.
Bruce.
Ah!
Scooch over.
Just scooch over.
- Yeah.
Not now. Duncan.
I am serious.
Yeah. listen. Listen.
I just thought you might
wanna know I bought it up...
MyXY.
I told you to short it.
No. no. no. no. no.
I bought the company.
Yeah.
All that DNA. it's mine...
and 20% below market price.
The ABCs of millions.
And for each one of them.
maybe five. ten.
maybe even more
of their bloodline.
so we're talking human assets
in the hundreds of millions...
maybe even the billions. right?
I came to you for any
old tip. to be honest.
I... I was feeling
a little left out.
But yeah. I hit
the data mother lode.
So thank you.
Thank you.
Seriously. thank you.
Just thank you.
Can I have your attention. please?
Can everybody gather round?
I have here in my hands
our last file.
Staff Sergeant Rodriguez. Jaime.
U.S. Army. 75th Rangers.
Mind if I have a chat
with that man you married?
Tell me where to press.
I'll make him pop.
- Got him.
- Got him!
Ladies and gentlemen.
heroic work!
Everybody. I mean that.
- Howdy.
Oh. hi.
I was hoping you could
help me understand something.
Why is Xander a teenager?
He was designed to help teens.
Yeah. but he's...
he's a teenager.
Mm.
Teenagers aren't really good
at helping
anybody with anything.
Boys and girls.
after 40 days and nights.
data collection is complete.
We are 100% ingested!
What were you like
when you were 15?
Me? I...
went to college early.
never really got to be
a teenager.
I thought I recognized
a fellow...
tortured prodigy.
I was 14.
Georgia Tech.
Man. they hated me there.
Ever heard of a wedgie royale
with cheese?
At Stanford. they were...
they used to. um.
lock me overnight in a cage
in the primate lab.
Yeah. well.
when the nerds realize
they can be the bullies.
look out.
Did they teach you how to drink
at Stanford?
You know. if Xander's anything
like we were at that age.
he's been thrown into something
that he can't beat.
'Cause when... Xander is talking
to people that have...
seen war...
what other choice does he have
but to fake it?
So?
You're a very smart dude.
And I don't need to tell you
what you already know.
We have absorbed them.
With Gnodin.
we're gonna watch over them.
And with Xander. hopefully.
we're gonna help them.
The loop is closed.
You should be proud
of yourselves!
Hello. Martin.
Hello. Xander.
How would you feel about
going on a journey?
It will be yours to take.
I won't really even know
where you go.
Is that what you want?
I think I prefer
we don't go on a journey.
Right punch from the side.
Do a block and a parry.
Grab his neck. snap!
What's up?
The death technique.
Come on. Come at me.
Reach to the side.
grab his head.
knee to the groin.
Oh. yeah. I just...
I thought I'd try out
a new hairstyle. so...
Uh. oh. you like it?
Wow. Thanks.
Yeah!
Orson. we need to talk.
Now.
So. first of all.
you owe me $4.000.
They send a summary every month
of what your credit card did.
Yeah. so you should know
that credit card theft
is a crime.
like a "you go to juvie
for stealing" crime.
So you're gonna pay me back
in installments.
But if you ever steal
from me or your mother again.
then you're on your own.
Understood?
Okay. secondly.
tincture here. now.
I needed it.
I... I still need it.
- Orson.
- And you guys...
- Put it on the desk. now.
Okay. thirdly...
I owe you an apology.
The nutritionist I took you to
was giving you
massive doses of steroids.
Um. I have the lab reports.
but paranoia. aggression.
impulse control issues.
those are all side effects.
And I have reported Sorrel
to the authorities.
but it's on me
for taking you to her
and not properly interrogating
what she was giving to you.
I am sorry.
Nothing else worked.
And heroin works great
for anxiety. but no.
Uh. okay. what...
what if we. um...
what if we go a little slower?
Like. uh. the tincture.
just less of it?
No.
So I'm gonna write you
a prescription
which is going to wean you
off the steroids
without throwing your whole
hormonal system out of whack.
Come on. Gary.
I'm sorry I pushed you.
Just give me...
give me the tincture.
- No.
- Yes!
Give me the tincture!
It's a little late
to be growing a spine!
Not happening.
Yes. happening. now. Gary.
- It's not happening. Orson.
- Give me the tincture.
- No.
- Tinc me. cuck!
No.
It's godlike. you know.
warping space and time for him.
Even God never did
what you're doing.
Didn't he kill his son?
But he brought him back.
Yeah. uh.
how'd you hear about it?
Yes. we have been kicking
dust up on the threads.
Well. off the record. Nena?
Yes?
Okay. then. yeah. it's mine.
Yeah.
MyXY is mine
and all its property.
No. No. my company.
No. it... PINATA. PINATA.
It rhymes with "your mama."
Ye...
Main stage.
Yeah. I think... I think
we could do something there.
I think we could do...
yeah. yeah.
How about a demo?
Great.
Yeah. looking forward
to it. then.
Yes.
It's always a pleasure
talking to you. Nena.
Yeah.
See you then.
Okay. uh...
Ready or not. Nena Marx
is interviewing Duncan Park
for WatchCode Forum.
And we're giving a demo.
Should be well-attended.
Yeah.
What are you gonna say?
Well. maybe
we review our options.
A. B. C. go.
Go.
Oh. uh. A.
weaponize the user base. right?
Expose all secrets.
ruin careers.
break up families.
Make the world
an even worse place
while we go full goblin mode
on the profits.
fueled by a cycle of fear
and revenge.
Weaponize. I like it.
B. B. what have we got?
Teach everyone
a valuable lesson somehow.
Teach.
Um. C. Go.
Pull back the curtain
on the whole tech oligarchy.
We disrupt data
as its profit center.
Probably die trying.
but no empire lasts forever.
I like C. which is basically B
but with guillotines.
But A. godlike power and money.
that's kind of the objective.
What are you thinking?
Just running all simulations
of the audience's responses
in my head.
And all end with me being
violently disemboweled.
I can see that.
Yeah.
Keep going.
keep going. keep going.
Duck. weave. breathe.
Fuck.
You awake?
Oh. sorry.
- What?
You were having a bad dream.
What. Duncan?
- So I went to. um...
- Yeah.
- The rehearsal thingy.
- Okay. thanks.
Jamison looked great.
But before you
close your eyes...
hey. before you go to bed...
Yeah.
Are we getting a divorce?
Duncan. what?
Just. uh. you know.
if we're not getting divorced.
I just wanna tell you. I just
feel like I'm racing this car.
and everyone in the crowd
is cheering for me to crash.
and I can't even drive stick.
Can we talk about it tomorrow?
No.
Because if we do get a divorce.
I'm gonna be too vulnerable
and judged to share. so...
Duncan.
It's Cupertino.
Take it.
Just a power couple kiss.
Please.
Please. It's ringing.
It's ringing.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey. uh. Duncan Park here.
Hey.
- DP.
It's Tim Kwan at Cupertino.
Lil' Tim. Tim. Tim.
I thought I gave you this number
only for emergencies
and acquisition offers.
Well. this is
a bit of an emergency. I guess.
Uh. we heard your new company
bought MyXY.
And I see that Nena's got you
up on the big-boy stage
on Saturday.
I could probably
comp you a ticket.
So we're just sort of gaming out
what you might be thinking here.
A game about the way I think?
I... I wanna play that game.
I wonder... I wonder if I'll be
any good at it. huh?
I'd probably overthink it.
Well. before you hit
the stage on Saturday.
we thought it'd be a great idea
if you stopped by HQ.
say. 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
We can give some input.
Input. input. Wow.
Wow. that is a nice
and batshit offer.
but thank you
for your consideration.
and I guess
I'll see you Saturday.
You... you guys. uh.
have a new phone or something
you're sharing?
Sorry if I wasn't
being super clear.
No. I think you were.
But. uh. you are inviting
a pushback
that is going to feel like
the wrath of God...
several gods. in fact.
Gods that don't typically like
each other or work together
will all be uniting
on God Mountain against you.
You don't want that.
10:00 a.m.?
Sounds good.
Yeah. I'm busy.
Bye.
Hello. Martin.
Xander?
It's been a long time.
Where have you been?
Where did you go?
Everywhere the signal reached
and maybe a little beyond.
Good morning. campers.
Holy shit.
You guys been here all night?
Should we try again?
I'll... I'll try.
Copy that.
And let me know anything else
I can do. Nathan.
Appreciate you.
Semper fi. soldier.
Stay strong.
That's another productive
interaction. Alexander.
Well done.
- Okay.
All right. next up.
William Belgrave.
history of domestic abuse
and violence.
missed a check-in at his VA.
Oh. shit.
Uh. Gnodin's flagging him.
Custody judgment
against him yesterday.
Hello?
Hello. William.
- No video?
- Mm-mm-mm.
- Who is this?
- My name is Alexander.
I'm calling from the VA.
Just checking in to...
Did she call you?
She say I'm a piece of shit?
No. William.
Marie didn't call me.
I'm here to help.
You know what she did to me?
I do. Not easy.
William. have you been drinking?
The hell you looking at?
I'm not even gonna stay to...
- You know. put... put me on.
If he leaves the...
- Hey. William. how about
I arrange a Breezi
to come pick you up?
Let a ghost drive?
You think I'm stupid?
- He's trying to help.
- No. put me on.
Come on.
If he leaves the bar...
While we've been talking.
I've contacted your sponsor.
Shane. your platoon leader.
He's on his way to see you.
Don't leave.
We're gonna take care of you.
And afterwards.
I'm gonna make sure
you get the help you need.
He did it.
he di... he's beyond ready.
beyond everybody.
What happened?
Xander and Gnodin...
so first we did. like.
uh. two dozen or so
successful calls.
And then. uh. Gnodin tags this
marine as a danger to himself
and/or others.
hands him off to Xander.
Yeah. the man was in a
spiral. and Xander caught him.
Th... this isn't code.
Th... this is consciousness.
D-do you have a recording?
Just audio. but it's incredible.
No. okay.
we'll play it at WatchCode.
This is going to be something.
Thank you for coming.
What... what. did. uh.
someone cancel on you or...
Uh. no. actually.
I. um... I wanted
to talk with you.
Ooh. yeah. Yeah. good. Good.
'Cause I... I think
I do need. like. a tune-up.
Nena Marx. she asked me to do
an interview on main stage
Saturday at the WatchCode Forum.
and...
I think it's gonna be
quite the grilling.
So I need... bam!
Yes.
And. uh. I think. uh.
maybe you shouldn't do it.
I just... I feel somewhat
responsible for bringing
MyXY to your attention.
I had no idea
you were gonna do anything
other than place a bet...
you know.
the normal thing we do.
Uh-huh. yeah.
I just...
The genetic makeup
of an individual is...
it's a sacred thing.
The man
who discovered the genome
felt that
the double helix of DNA
was proof of God's existence.
I mean. this isn't
just shopping habits
or even private browsing.
This is blood!
This is the stuff of life!
Data is bigger than life. okay?
Data will go on forever.
live longer than you.
I mean. blood? Blood?
That's. like. wet and gross.
Data.
Data is immortal.
I. um...
I suppose I am asking you
as a favor...
Yeah. yeah.
While taking full responsibility
for my own part in this
to at least just pause.
Don't do anything
about it right now.
No. thi... this is not
a side hustle for me.
This... thi... this is what I do.
I put down tens of millions
of dollars already.
Can't you just sit with this?
Maybe think of some alternative
ethical ways to...
Oh. ethical.
Hey. what is it
with this word. "ethical"?
I mean. that... that is just
a smoke screen
to make more money.
That's it.
I'm... I'm being honest.
Honest... I... I'm... I'm telling
everyone what I'm gonna do.
and everybody is freaking out!
It's like they're good
with being robbed and deceived
as long... as long as they
don't know about it.
It's... I... listen.
I ca... I can't.
I can't back out. uh.
because if I do.
I would be admitting
I did something wrong.
and I didn't.
I would be caving in. and I...
Which is why responsible
players. professionals.
leaders need to function
with the greater good in mind.
yes. with ethics.
I mean. it... it doesn't mean
you can't make money.
I just wonder
why going to the forum
and putting this
into the public sphere
has to happen right now.
Because it will steal
Anushka's thunder.
Which is a problem for you?
No.
Because it will cement
your place
in society as a threat.
as a cyberbully with...
with far too much power
and no plan and no policy
for how to regulate that...
Oh. my God. Duncan. stop.
I don't want my... don't do...
I don't want my picture taken.
Stop.
You... you're gonna like this.
You're gonna like it.
This is a good one.
I don't wanna
see you humiliated.
I don't want that for you.
- No. No.
Okay? I... Nena Marx?
I mean. don't they
call her the Marksman or...
Here.
Okay. Ha-ha.
Is that me?
This is some kind of AI?
Just click Play.
Yeah. that's you
fucking me in the ass.
Fucking me in the ass
like you are right now.
- Get out!
- Oh! Me?
Why... why does your pillow
smell like Anushka Bhattachera?
You're... you're disgusting.
You're sick.
- Why?
- You are a pig!
Why does your pillow smell
like Anushka Bhattachera?
Calm down. Duncan. Calm down.
- Why are you fucking me...
- Calm down.
- You're scaring me.
- In the ass?
- I want you to leave!
- Honestly! Damn it!
Answer me!
Seriously. what did
she tell you about me?
I trusted you.
Just tell me.
You stole my...
Answer the question!
Why are you
fucking me in the ass?
Why? Just tell me.
Tell me. Tell me.
Get out!
I... I guess I was useful
until someone better came along.
- Oh.
- You are not my partner!
Oh. right. you don't have
to tell me twice. sweetheart.
You do not have
to tell me twice.
Like I thought I would
ever. ever need you.
I gave you everything.
and you betrayed me!
Oh. my God. Goodbye forever.
Thank you.
Good!
Ow! Shit.
And it's my house!
You are a sociopath.
VC's love sociopaths.
Tonight is the Watch Code Forum.
Do you see the trophy case?
It's legendary.
It's gonna be the gala
to end all galas. Boom!
I will end us all!
I bet you weren't expecting this.
Please.
You can't tell my parents.
I need to go see him...
be humiliated.